Didiek Trisatya

Student University

**** 087730234000

https://my-portfoliotrisatya.herokuapp.com/

Tegal, Central Java

EXPERIENCE

Mobile Programmer

PT Bisa Artifisial Indonesia

02/2022 - 07/2022

- Build mobile app SIAKAD with Android Studio
- · Collaborate with Backend Developer

Frontend Engineer

PT Solusi Tiket Digital

10/2021 - 01/2022

- Create a website with React JS + Ionic
- · Collaborate with UI/UX Design
- · Collaborate with Backend Developer

Web Developer

Youth Empowerment Indonesia (YOE)

02/2021 - 05/2021

- Create a website with Codeigniter 3
- Collaborate with UI/UX Design

Frontend Developer

PT Inspirasi Mandiri Nusantara

09/2020 - 01/2021

- · Develop the appearance of the company website
- Collaborate with Backend Developers & UI/UX Design
- · Update company website regularly

SUMMARY

Informatics Engineering Student at Dian Nuswantoro University. My current expertise is in web development.

I am in the process of learning many new things, so by the time I graduated from university I was ready to be placed anywhere to work.

SKILLS

React JS Intermediate
Android Studio Intermediate
Laravel Intermediate
Git Advanced
Postman Advanced

LANGUAGES

Indonesian Native
English Intermediate

EDUCATION

Informatics Engineering

Universitas Dian Nuswantoro

2023

Bachelor's Degree

CERTIFICATES

TCS iON Career Edge - Young Professional

01/2021 - Present

Aviatrix Certified Engineer - Multi-Cloud Network Associate Course

08/2020 - Present

Google Digital Enterpreneurship

08/2020 - Present